IMAGINE A TYPICAL
SUNDAY AFTERNOON A
COUPLE IS DRIVING
TO A DINNER
PARTY THE MAN
MISSES A TURN
THE WOMAN IMMEDIATELY
SAYS HEY HONEY
YOU SHOULD HAVE
TURNED THERE WHY
DON'T YOU PULL
OVER AND CHECK
GOOGLE MAPS HERE
LET ME HOLD
THE PHONE FOR
YOU NOTICE WHAT
JUST HAPPENED HERE
IN HER MIND
SHE IS DEMONSTRATING
PURE UNSELFISH LOVE
SHE IS HELPING
SHE IS NURTURING
IN HIS SUBCONSCIOUS
THE TRANSLATION IS
LETHAL HE DOESN'T
HEAR I LOVE
YOU HE HEARS
I DON'T TRUST
YOUR JUDGMENT I
THINK YOU'RE INCAPABLE
HE GRIPS THE
STEERING WHEEL HIS
JAW LOCKS AND
HE SNAPS BACK
WITH AN IRRITABLE
TONE I KNOW
WHERE I'M GOING
SHE IS LEFT
SHOCKED AND HURT
WHY ARE YOU
BITING MY HEAD
OFF I WAS
JUST TRYING TO
HELP WELCOME TO
THE INVISIBLE WAR